<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Socratica Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Socratica Toolbox</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>The Basics</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/basics</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/basics</guid>
    <description>What is Socratica? § TLDR: We assemble kind, nerdy, and ambitious young people that are dedicated to consistently creating. We’re united by a couple of core beliefs: There are increasingly few, low stakes ways for young people to make interest, values aligned friends IRL These spaces need to be recurring, consistent, and accessible.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:15:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Cultivating People</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/cultivating-people</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/cultivating-people</guid>
    <description>How to organize spaces that feel awesome § Picture yourself entering a Socratica session. What do you feel? What do you want the participants to feel? How do hosts ensure that Socratica remains inclusive, beginner-friendly, and a good time? Balance is key § People want to be in spaces where they feel like they can bring their full self.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 23:52:07 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Getting Started</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/getting-started</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/getting-started</guid>
    <description>When you know you should start a node Owner: Jacky Zhao jakesrudolph7@gmail.com Status: Initial write complete, looking for input!! In short, you should considering starting a node if: You want this for yourself You have faith that there are good people around you You are willing to put in the work to cultivate this Note that neither of these include specific personality traits.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 22:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Welcome to Socratica</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/</guid>
    <description></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:13:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Maintenance</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/maintenance</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/maintenance</guid>
    <description>How to handoff to new hosts Owner: Ananya Anupam, Rishi Kothari Status: Initial write incomplete, owned &amp; open to contributors Beyond fostering spaces for amazing work, longevity should be one of the primary areas of focus for nodes.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 22:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Superboosting Ideas</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/superboosting-ideas</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/superboosting-ideas</guid>
    <description>Types of Ideas Owner: @jake Status: Initial write incomplete, owned &amp; open to contributors A core pillar of building a community for people to see the best version of their ideas is to understand ideas, how they progress over time, and how you can support your people at each stage of their idea.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 22:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>